早上好
Morning.
-嘿 -你睡得好吗
- Hey. - You sleep all right?
没睡好 你呢
No, you?
-说没有 菲尔 -当然没有
- Say no, Phil. - Of course no.
我一直在想你
I missed you up there.
昨晚 我知道我有点过激...
Last night, I know I got kind of carried away --
不不不 你不需要抱歉
No, no, no. You don't need to apologize.
我可不觉得我是在道...
I don't think that I was apologi--
你有理由生气
You were right to be mad.
有时候我觉得只有尖叫
Sometimes I just feel like I have to scream
才能让你知道我有多沮丧
to let you know how upset I am,
但是你现在明白了 对吧
but you get it now, right?
我 明白了
I...do.
才怪
Not.
完全摸不着头脑
No idea whatsoever.
如果我知道 但是
Ohh, if I knew, but...
我真的不知道
no.
很好
Good.
我们就假装这件事从未发生过
So let's pretend the whole thing never happened.
是啊 我们为了什么事而争吵啊
What were we even fighting about, huh?
这里发生什么事了
What the heck happened in here?
又有浣熊从狗洞钻进来了吗
The raccoon get through the dog door again?
是的 有浣熊进来了
Yep. The raccoon got in,
你妈妈用灭火器把它赶跑了
and your mom fought it off with the fire extinguisher.
你看起来乱糟糟的
You're a mess!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
小心点 伙计 今天不要惹你妈
Careful, buddy. Not today.
我认为你看起来美极了
I think you look beautiful.
省省吧
Save it.
有一次我忘了给歌洛莉亚买生日礼物
One time I forgot to get Gloria a birthday present,
我为此付出了代价
and I paid for it.
有一次我虽记得 但她却不喜欢那个礼物
Another time I remembered, but she didn't like the gift.
我为那也付出了代价
I paid for that.
那么你会想 如果我记得她的生日
So you'd think when I remember to buy her a gift
她又刚好喜欢那个礼物
and she loves it,
那我就不必遭殃了 对吧
I wouldn't have to pay for it, right?
叫我早上滴天使 天使
Just call me angel of the morning, angel
在你走之前 虎摸我的脸颊 宝贝
Just touch my cheek before you leave me, baby
很好
Oh, hey, good.
抓住这个桌子的另一边 帮我把它抬出去
Grab the other end of this and help me get it out of here.
我要开始为今晚准备椅子了
I have to start setting up the chairs for tonight.
-今晚 今晚有什么 -开什么玩笑
- Oh, tonight? What's tonight? - Are you kidding me?
我就是我一直纠结的地方 米奇尔
This is what I'm talking about Mitchell.
你总是把我的话当耳旁风 当我...
You never listen when I --
这是一个为第三街立交桥音乐之友协会的
It's a fundraiser for the friends
朋友们举办的筹集资金的活动
of the third street overpass music society.
会有两个竖琴师来表演
Two harpists are performing,
你很焦虑 因为安德鲁
and you're anxious 'cause Andrew,
他是你在督导委员会的宿敌
Your nemesis from the steering committee,
他去年举办了这个活动
ran the event last year,
而你想全面超越他的那次
and you want to upstage him.
我是开玩笑的
I was kidding.
小卡总是认为
Cam has it in his head
我不听他说话 但其实我有听
that I don't listen to him, but I do.
有在听吗 米奇尔 有吗
Do you, Mitchell? Do you?
医生打电话来说
The doctor called and said
莉莉没得皮疹 那只是皮肤干燥
Lily's rash is just dry skin.
我终于可以松口气了
I'm so relieved.
我刚对你说了什么
What did I just say?
你表现得你会听我讲述每一件事
You act like you listen to every single thing that I say,
但其实你没有
but you don't.
我没有吗 米奇尔
Don't I, Mitchell?
我今天会去商店
Hey, I'm going to the store today.
你要我给你带点什么吗
Do you need me to pick anything up for you?
刀片 生理盐水 黑袜
Razor blades, saline solution, black socks,
和新出版的《名利场》
and the new issue of Vanity Fair.
我都不记得我要你给我买这些
Wow. I don't even remember asking for all that.
谢谢
Thank you.
我没有吗
Don't I?
这个到底是怎么掉下来的
How'd this thing come off, anyway?
我在做晚餐
Well, I was cooking dinner, and --
是的
Right.
一只浣熊突然就进来了
And the raccoon just walked in the --
我已经把这个打开了
And I already had the door open.
-是的 -我也已经抓住
- Right. - Which I-I had already had ahold of the --
你们两个为什么不去把故事编好再回来
Why don't you two go work on your story and come back?
-好的 -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
我今晚会很晚回家
I won't be home till late.
我在餐厅又有一次轮班
I have another shift at the restaurant.
这才是我们的上班女郎
That's our working girl.
让河流流淌吧 亲爱的
Let the river run, honey.
看 昨晚的57美元小费
Check it! $57 in tips from last night.
亲爱的 这真是太棒了 你知道吗
Honey, that's impressive. You know what?
你的57美元 再加上我们的57美元
$57 from you, $57 from us --
你继续下去的话
You keep this up,
这个夏天我们就可以给你买辆车
we are going to be buying you a car by the summer.
妈妈 这是高档休闲装吗
Mom, is this "upscale casual"?
什么
What?
是的 小卡雇了卢克
Oh, yeah. Cam hired Luke
要他帮忙今晚的慈善活动
to help out with the benefit tonight.
你知道吗 我修不好这个
Hey, you know what? I can't fix this thing.
什么 我需要它 我每天都得用它
What? I need that. I use it every day.
好吧 菲尔 你说呢
Okay, Phil, what do you say?
你想跟我一起去购物中心吗
You want to take a trip to the mall with me?
想去
I...do.
才怪
Not,
我能闪就闪
if I can possibly avoid it.
克莱尔在购物中心有个
Claire has this little...habit...
小小的习惯 她
at the mall, where sh--
我甚至都说不出口
I can't even talk about it.
杰 快点
Jay, come on!
我想回家
I want to go home
因为你说要录下我唱K时的情景
because you said you were going to film me doing the
我就可以把带子寄到哥伦比亚我妈那
karaoke so I can send it to Colombia to my mother.
克莱尔 去购物中心
Claire, um, about the mall?
我下午其实要去外面
I was actually gonna run out
把头发剪了
and get my hair cut this afternoon.
等一下
Well, hang on here.
为什么不让我跟克莱尔去购物中心
Why don't I run claire down the mall,
你来给菲尔理发
and you give Phil a haircut?
你不是总是在讲
You're always talking about
你很想念发廊的工作吗
how you miss working at the salon.
我想我可以的
I guess I could.
我能帮杰做 为什么不能帮你做呢
I do jay. Why can't I do you?
你可以"做"我
You...can do me.
好的 我们让派对开始
Okay, let's get this party started.
你知道那首歌吗
You know that song?
我们快走 快走 我们在浪费时间
Let's go, let's go! We're wasting time!
-好的 好的 -知道
- O-okay, okay. - Yeah.
-你知道吗 -我想是的
- You know it? - I think I do.
那么 刚刚那是安德鲁
So, that was Andrew,
他几乎是哽咽着跟我说
who practically choked telling me
没有人致电表示很抱歉
that no one had called in their regrets
参加不了今天的活动
for the event tonight.
今晚一定是座无虚席
It is gonna be a full house.
那一定让你感觉很爽
Oh, that must feel great!
我从未想过我会享受宿敌的存在
Oh, I never thought I would enjoy having an arch enemy. Oh.
但是 我很享受 米奇尔 很享受
But I do, Mitchell. I do. Hmm.
莉莉 你在玩什么呢
Hey, Lily, what you got there?
我真为PETA的那些人感到难过
I do feel bad for those PETA folks.
他们的活动也是在今晚
Their event's tonight, too.
所以我才老早就让你把邀请函寄出去
That's why I had you mail the invitations so long ago.
我不应该笑的
I shouldn't laugh.
我确实为那些动物感到难过
I do feel bad for those little PETA animals.
真的
I really do.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
没什么 她在
Nothing. She was, uh --
她又在吸吮她的大拇指
she was, uh, sucking her thumb again.
没错 我把小卡的邀请函放在车上
Yes, I put Cam's invites in my car
准备带去邮局的
to take them to the post office
但我把我的健身包放在那上面了
and then threw my gym bag on top of them
完全忘记它们的存在了
and completely forgot they existed.
我感觉糟透了
Ohh, I feel terrible.
六周没有去健身房了
Haven't been to the gym in six weeks.
而且还把小卡的活动搞砸了
And I ruined Cam's event.
你好 哈特威克女士
Hello, Miss Hartwick.
小卡和我今天晚上
Uh, Cam and I are hosting
举办一个小型活动
a little event tonight, and --
是的 是的
Yes, yes.
不 我知道今晚PETA也会有活动
No, I am aware that there is also a PETA event,
还有
and -- ohh.
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
我在冲凉
I'm in the shower!
卢克 椅子摆的怎么样了
Luke, how are those chairs coming?
呼叫
Come in.
我想你应该来看看 呼叫
I think you should come in come in.
现在我很担心连贯性
Oh, now I'm worried about the flow.
他们应该看着竖琴 而不是椅背
The eyes should go to the harps, not the backs of chairs.
你会变得情绪低落
Are you gonna get upset
然后又把所有的开胃菜都吃掉吗
and starting eating all the appetizers again?
你注意到的和没注意到的事情真让人吃惊
It is amazing what you notice and what you don't notice.
请你处理一下 我需要想想
Please handle that. I need to think.
给点力 卢克
Come on, Luke.
你好 你爸爸在家吗
Hi, there. Your father home?
应该在家 怎么了
I think so. Why?
是接待人员
Oh, oh! The wait staff.
卢克 请把他们领到厨房去
Please, luke, show them to the kitchen, please.
有人吗
Knock knock.
你好 安德鲁
Oh. Hello, Andrew.
椅背看起来不错
Nice chair backs.
我想你会用得上这个
I just thought you could use this.
这是我去年活动的签名簿
It's the sign-in book for my event last year.
让我们翻到空白页
Let just turn to the blank pages,
那是在
Which should be...
不 全写满了
Oh. No. It's full.
谢谢你为我们着想
Oh, well, thank you for thinking of us,
但是你不是应该回家去陪唐纳德吗
but shouldn't you be getting back home to Donald?
那是你猫咪的名字 不是吗
That is the name of your cat, isn't it?
我们七点见
I'll see you at 7:00.
开车小心点
Drive safely.
我跟你说什么来着
What did I tell you?
她比你说的还差劲
She's even worse than you said.
别动
Hold still!
你不能像这样动来动去
You can't move like that.
这就像在剪布谷鸟的头发一样
It's like cutting the hair of a cuckoo bird.
对不起 我今天有点神经紧绷
I'm sorry. I'm just a little tense today.
我就知道 有事发生了
I knew it. Something happened.
因为当某人在发廊工作时
Because when somebody works in a salon,
有人需要谈心 他们总能发现
they know when someone needs to talk.
事实上 或许你可以帮我解决这个问题
Actually, you might be able to help me with this one.
克莱尔昨晚和我大吵了一架
Claire and I got into a huge fight last night...
我甚至都不知道因为什么
...and I'm not even sure what it was about.
这就是为什么你不跟她去购物中心的原因吗
Was that why you didn't want to go to the mall with her?
不是 那是因为
No, that was... more about a weird...
克莱尔怪异的商场习惯
mall habit claire has.
天呐 真舒服
Oh, my god! That's good!
天呐 低一点 再低一点
Oh, oh! Go low, go low.
低一点 低一点
Go low, go low. Oh! Oh!
天呐
Oh, my god!
老爸老爸
Dad! Dad!
你一定要买一个
You got to get one of these! Oh!
海莉的收入真是让人乍舌
It is impressive how much Haley's earning.
她已经赚了五百多美元
She's over $500 already.
那可是能买很多切达干酪啊
That's a lot of cheddar.
为什么大家都表现的
Why's everyone acting
好像她是首个十七岁有工作的人一样
like she's the first 17-year-old to have a job?
在其他文明中 她都应该有两个孩子了
In other cultures, she'd have two kids already,
孩子们都有工作了
and they'd have jobs.
我去了那个餐厅好几次
You know, I stopped by the restaurant a couple times,
她都不在那里
and she wasn't there.
什么时候
When?
我不记得了
Uh, I don't remember.
我在购物中心看电影
I was at the mall for a movie.
想想 我要知道细节
Think! I need details!
好吧 那是个浪漫的喜剧
Okay, it was a romantic comedy
是我以前的朋友鲁本推荐的
My now ex-friend Reuben recommended --
不是说电影 是哪一天 仔细想
Not about the movie! What day?! Focus!
好吧 是周二
Okay, uh, it was Tuesday,
但我周六也去那里吃饭了
But I also ate there again on Saturday,
她还是不在那里
and she wasn't there then, either.
天呐
Oh, my god.
我打赌她都不在那里工作
I bet she doesn't even work there.
那么 那些钱是哪里来的呢
Well, then, where's all this money coming from?
你注意到每晚
Do you notice how every single night
都正好是少于六十美元吗
is just under $60?
她生日的时候姥爷给了她六十美元
Grandpa gave her $60 for her birthday.
她整天去商场无所事事
She's just hanging around the mall all day,
每晚亮出同一笔钱
flashing the same cash every night,
骗我爸妈去给她买辆车
and fooling my parents into buying her a car.
老爸
Hey, dad!
我们今晚能去海莉的餐馆吃饭吗
Can we eat at Haley's restaurant tonight?!
很好啊
Hey, there's a good idea!
真棒 我发短信告诉她
Great. I'll text her.
天呐 不会吧
Oh, god, no!
天呐 真棒
Oh, god, yes!
Oh! Oh, god, yes!
继续
Oh, get after it!
太棒了
Amazing.
我想再试一刻钟
I'm going for 15 more on me.
我觉得你已经体验够了
I think you got what you needed from that.
好吧 谢谢
Oh. Okay. Thank you.
你是不是应该跟我谈谈吵架的事情
You know, maybe you do need to talk about this fight.
和菲尔吗
With Phil?
你怎么会不知道她生气的原因
How could you not know what she was mad about?
因为她没告诉我啊 她直接就发狂了
Because she didn't tell me. She just freaked out.
我真是受不了你了 菲尔
I cannot believe you, Phil!
你怎么能这样
How could you?!
怎么了 我 我干了什么
What is happening? What -- what did I do?
不是吧你
Are you serious?
你当真 你真不知道
You are! You don't know.
我们都已经谈过一百遍了
We've had this conversation a hundred times.
你知道 不 不
You know -- no, no.
我不会再说一遍了
I'm not -- I'm not doing this again.
你告诉我你做了什么
You tell me what you did.
-是不是 -"是不是"
- Was it -- - "Was it --"
别说了 菲尔
No, Phil.
算了算了算了
No. No, no, no. No!
-我要去透透气 -克莱尔
- I'm going to get some air. - Claire.
-克莱尔 -别叫我 别跟着我
- Claire! -No! Don't follow me.
情人生日纪念日快乐
Happy valen-birth-iversary!
气呼呼的离开
Storming off --
和你老妈如出一辙
right out of yr mom's playbook.
然后你去了哪里
Where'd you go?
结果 我没有走远
Well, as it turns out, not very far.
见鬼
Damn it.
菲尔
Phil!
菲尔 你个蠢货 停下
Phil, you moron, stop it!
-是我 你个蠢货 -对不起
- It's me, you idiot! - I'm sorry!
你在干什么
What are you doing?!
对不起
I'm sorry!
我以为是只浣熊
I thought you were a raccoon!
你以为我是只浣熊
You thought I was a raccoon!
因为人看上去像是浣熊
Because people look so much like raccoons.
你看
Oh, look.
这儿就有一只
There's one now!
不要啊 克莱尔 不要 克莱尔
No, claire, no! Claire!
等等
Wait a minute.
疯女人发疯都是有原因的
Not even crazy woman go crazy for no reason.
西兰花之前发生了什么
What happened before the broccoli?
问题就 她突然就爆发了啊
That's just it -- it came out of the blue.
我走进门
I walked in the door,
我们就随便聊聊
we're having a conversation about nothing.
亲爱的
Hey, honey.
抱歉单位有点事耽搁了
Sorry I got stuck at the office.
今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
不错
It was good.
-你知道发生了什么吗 -什么
- Although you know what? - What?
黛比午饭放我鸽子了
Debbie stood me up for lunch.
很无礼是吧
Rude, right?
没有啊 她打电话
No. She called.
我没有收到消息啊
I didn't get a message.
你收到了
Yeah. You did.
我给你留字条了
I left you one.
就在这儿
It's right...there.
那就是原因
That's it!
她怎么可能看见这个
How is she supposed to see this?
你要是给我这么小的纸条
If you give me a message this tiny,
我会杀了你
I kill you.
但她不是那时候发狂的
But that's not when she got mad.
我还和保险公司的人谈了谈
Also, I talked to the insurance company
就是那个"不是你的错"小事故
about that little accident that "wasn't your fault"
因为刹车"不正常"
because the brakes weren't "working right."
而且赔的钱也没有我想的多
And that's not gonna cost us as much money as I thought,
很好
so that's good.
那就是原因
That's it!
你侮辱一个女人的驾驶技术
You insult a woman's driving,
你还用了手指兔子
and you use the "air bunnies."
你要是对我那样做 我会杀了你
You do that to me, and I kill you.
了解
I hear you,
但是发狂也不是从那时开始的
but the screaming still hadn't started yet.
我不是和斯基普·伍斯纳吃午饭的吗
So, I'm having lunch with Skip Woosnum, right?
天呐 那家伙说个不停
Boy, can that guy go on and on.
都不知道说哪去了
Tangent after tangent.
对了 他还让我对一个超赞的东西产生了兴趣
By the way, turned me on to the greatest thing --
卷心菜沙拉 你应该试试
wedge salad -- you gotta try it.
随便了
Anyhoo...
你猜谁和我们邻桌
Guess who's sitting at the table next to us.
我前女友卡拉
My old girlfriend Carla.
我们打算一起去喝咖啡
We're gonna grab coffee.
她瘦了不少
She lost a ton of weight.
你怎么这么蠢
How stupid are you?
你要是跟我说你去见前女友 我就
You tell me that you're seeing an old girlfriend, and I --
杀了我 我知道
Kill me, I know.
但是她那时还没有爆发
But she still hadn't snapped yet.
差点忘了
I almost forgot.
我买了你要的西兰花
I picked up the broccoli you asked for.
花椰菜
Cauliflower.
真不敢相信我又买错了
Can't believe I did that again.
真是受不了你了 菲尔
I cannot believe you, Phil!
你不是做错一件事
You didn't do one thing wrong.
每件事都做错了
You do everything wrong!
我都不知道她为什么还要跟你说话
I don'even know why she talks to you.
她说她没事的
She said she was okay.
不 没有女人会对这种事释怀的
No. No woman is okay with this.
我们不会忘记
We don't forget.
我们等着
We wait.
然后 在你最不经意的时候
And then, when you least expect it,
让你付出应有的代价
we make you pay.
下巴抬起来
Chin up!
抬起来
Up!
这么说你因为那事发飙了
So you had a meltdown over that.
是的 因为自打我遇见他
I did, because ever since I met him,
我就想让菲尔试试卷心菜沙拉
I've been trying to get Phil to try a wedge salad.
斯基普·伍斯纳这个他并不喜欢的人
The minute that Skip Woosnum,
一推荐这个
whom he doesn't even like, suggests it,
菲尔就觉得这是最好的东西
Phil thinks it's the greatest thing ever,
每一件事都是这样
and he does this with everything.
书 电影 还有电视 都是这样
He does it with books, with movies, with tv.
他听取所有人的意见 除了我的
He listens to everybody's opinion but mine,
这都让我抓狂了
And it drives me crazy.
你们俩今早看上去没事啊
You two seemed fine this morning.
是啊 因为我们讨论过了
Well, we were because we talked about it,
顺便说下
which, by the way,
你要是想解决歌洛莉亚唱K这件事
if you want this whole karaoke thing with Gloria to go away,
你就应该这么做
That's what you need to do.
说着容易做着难
That's easier said than done.
你什么时候开始回避正面冲突了
Well, since when do you shy away from confrontation,
强硬先生 直话直说先生
Mr. Tough Talk, Mr. Straight shooter?
变得温和了吗 老爷子
Getting a little soft, grandpa?
别人给你做按摩的时候
You know, when you get a massage,
你发出的声音就像是蒂华纳的妓女
you sound like a Tijuana prostitute.
卢克 电话
Luke, phone.
第三街的朋友
Friends of the third street --
是米奇尔吗 他怎么这么慢
Is that Mitchell? What's taking him?
不是 不是米奇尔 是
No, it's not Mitchell. It's...
我不明白他的名字
I don't understand his name.
哪位
Hello?
兰吉尼斯 你好 听着
Oh, hi, Longinus. Listen,
你收到我的消息了吗
did you get my message?
关于那个竹节椅的那条
About the chiavari chairs --
我想你过来的时候带给我
I want you to bring them when you come.
你不来 是什么意思
What do you mean you're not -- not coming?
那不可能
Well, that's not possible.
米奇 米奇两礼拜前就发邀请给他们了
Mitch -- Mitch mailed them weeks ago.
那派珀呢 他收到了吗
What about Pepper? Did he get his?
那迈克尔呢
And Michael?
那史蒂夫和斯特凡呢
And Steven and Stefan?
还有鲍勃
And Bob?
我得挂了
I have to go.
打给你米奇尔舅舅
Get me your uncle Mitchell.
我不知道他号码
I don't know his number.
转到语音信箱了
It went to voicemail.
当然了
Of course it did.
一直打 直到接通
Keep trying him until you get him.
只需一个键
it's one button.
只要 重拨
Just...redial.
今晚的盛大活动
Hey, really great event tonight
回报音乐社会 回报像你一样的音乐家
benefiting the music society -- musicians like you.
小卡舅舅呼叫米奇尔舅舅
Uncle Cam for uncle Mitchell.
你怎么能这样 米奇尔
How could you, Mitchell?!
说真的 给我
Honestly! Give me that.
你想听听今晚的客人名单吗
You want to hear the guest list for night?
目前有气愤 背叛 恐怖和伤心
So far it's anger, betrayal, terror, and sadness.
恭喜你 米奇尔 屋子里全塞满了
Congratulations, Mitchell, you packed the house!
小卡 我真的很抱歉
Cam, I am so sorry.
我会搞定的 我会捐一大笔钱
I-I-I'm gonna fix it. I'll make a big donation.
那也阻止不了他们
That's not gonna keep them
把我踢出督导委员会
from kicking me off the steering committee!
当安德鲁走进来
When Andrew walks in here
发现这间房里全是空着的椅子
and sees a room full of empty chairs --
他并不是你的宿敌
You know he's not really your archenemy.
那只是你幻想的
That's sort of a made-up thing.
搞定它
Fix it!
-你来了 -嗨
- Hi! You came! - Hi!
当然得来了 我们想看你工作的样子
Of course we did. We wanted to see you work.
我们真为你感到骄傲 甜心
We're so proud of you, sweetheart.
我们都感到自豪 我们的桌子在哪
Yeah, we're all proud. So where's our table?
其实 有个坏消息
Actually, bad news.
我们这里都被订满了
We totally booked.
我们有超多的预定
We have a ton of reservations.
是的 有一份是我们的 我预定了
Yeah, one's ours. I called.
就在这
Here it is!
那么你们的桌子就在这里
Uh, so, your table is right here.
亲爱的 能给我们拿几杯饮料吗
Oh, honey, would you mind getting us a couple drinks?
我要一杯冰茶
I would love an iced tea.
我也是
Same, please.
我要芒果-奇异果沙冰
I'll have a mango-kiwi smoothie,
把冰淇淋换成酸奶 要低脂的
yogurt instead of ice cream, and make it low-fat.
当我坐你的新车时 我得看起来很漂亮
I want to look good when I'm riding in your new car.
亲爱的 我得说
Honey, I got to say,
我喜欢这个发型
I like this haircut.
在这个家里 我们都只是第二名 你才最棒
Hey, we're all just playing for second in this family.
你喝完了吗
Were you all done here?
没有
Uh, actually, no.
我还要一杯冰茶
Um, I will have more iced tea,
再来一杯冰茶
Another iced tea,
还有一个芒果-奇异果的沙冰
and a mango-kiwi smoothie,
全是冰淇淋的
all ice cream.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
这很不错
Well, this is nice.
我 我的女儿们
Me, my gals,
还有我美丽 漂亮的媳妇
and my beautiful, beautiful wife.
你得知道 我跟卡拉重新约定了时间
Just so you know, I rescheduled with Carla.
我约了她12号见面
I penciled her in for the 12th...
没说月份
of never.
那太糟了
That's too bad.
我还蛮希望听到点八卦的
I was kind of looking forwd to hearing about that one.
顺便告诉你
By the way,
你出去之后没人打电话找你
no one called for you while you were out.
要谢谢你吗
Thank you?
我只想确定你能接到任何朋友的留言
I just want to make sure you get any messages
但是没有人打来
from any friends who might call, which none of them did.
海莉是这里唯一一个没带名牌的
Isn't it weird that Haley's the only one here
这不是很奇怪吗
not wearing a name tag?
如果你妈妈有个名牌的话
If your mother had a name tag,
上面会写着"好司机"
it would say "Good driver."
-菲尔 -这是你们点的
- Phil -- - Here you go.
很流行的 说了你也不懂
Popular, which you wouldn't understand.
还有什么能比
Well, what could be better
和一个美女喝两杯更好
than drinks with a beautiful woman?
每个漂亮的女人都值得拥有鲜花
And every beautiful woman deserves flowers.
花椰菜
Cauliflowers.
好吧 怎么回事 是因为昨晚的事吗
Okay. What's going on? Is this about last night?
是的 我只想让你知道你对我有多重要
Yeah, I just want you to know how important to me you are.
亲爱的 我知道 我知道
Sweetie, I know that. I know that.
我还是感觉很糟
I still feel bad about, you know
因为我的所作所为
what I...did.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们没事
You and I are fine.
好吗
Okay?
我真的很饿了
I'm just really hungry.
好吗
Okay?
好的
Okay.
那行
All right!
什么看起来好吃呢
What looks good?
天啊
Oh, gosh.
有东西从这一页跳出来了
Ooh, here's something that jumps right off the page.
我昨天吃过这道菜
Uh-huh. I tried this yesterday,
多亏我朋友斯基普·伍斯纳的推荐
thanks to my good friend Skip Woosnum.
克莱尔 帮自己一个忙
Claire, do yourself a favor
跟我一起来一份卷心菜沙拉吧
and join me in a wedge salad.
你不是在跟我开玩笑吧
You have got to be kidding me!
只要尝一口 你就会感谢我的
Just try it. You will thank me.
通过昨晚的事 你什么都没学到吗
Did you learn nothing from last night?
是因为沙拉吗
It was about the salad?
几年来 我一直推荐卷心菜沙拉给你
I have been recommending wedge salads to you,
还有别的东西
amongst other things, for years,
但你从来都不听我的
and you never listen to me.
然后某个蠢蛋向你推荐
And then some idiot suggests it,
你就等不及想去吃卷心菜沙拉
and you can't wait to try a wedge salad?!
这让我觉得我不重要
It makes me feel like I don't matter.
太感谢你了 老爸
Thanks a lot, dad!
妈妈的小发作让我被解雇了
Mom's little outburst just got me fired!
好的 我得去跟你妈妈谈谈
Okay, I got to talk to your mom.
你去安慰你的姐姐
You comfort your sister.
她从未在这里工作过
She never worked here!
米奇尔也给你打电话了
So, Mitchell called you, too.
我想你还没跟歌洛莉亚谈过
I take it you haven't had your conversation with Gloria yet?
情况更糟了
It's getting worse.
来的时候 她唱了一路
She sang all the way here.
我们经过两辆车
We passed two cars --
车里的狗都把头缩回车内了
the dogs stuck their heads back inside the window.
我们接下来该怎么做
What are we gonna do?
-我可以点一场大火 -不
- I could start a fire. - No.
把这个当做备用对策
Keep that in your back pocket.
我想给你看点东西
I want to show you something.
让我猜一猜
Let me guess.
是一本我求了你很久
It's a copy of "The Book Thief"
叫你去读读的叫《偷书贼》的书
that I begged you to read,
直到你的牙科医生说这本书改变了她的一生
but you wouldn't until your dental hygienist
你才去读的
said it changed her life.
-记得这个吗 -是啊
- Remember this? - Uh-huh.
这是我跟你家人度过的第一个感恩节
It's the first thanksgiving I spent with your family.
天 我真讨厌那马尾辫
God, I hated that ponytail.
我知道
I know.
你说它让我看起来像一个懦弱的保镖
You said it made me look like a wimpy bouncer,
所以我就把它剪了
so I cut it off.
就像我摘掉了羽毛耳环
Just like I lost the feathered earring...
还有豆袋椅面包车
and the van with the beanbag chairs.
而且我也换了我的专业
And I changed my forestry major.
我明白 菲尔 我明白
I get it, Phil. I get it.
我就是个控制欲极强的巫婆
I am the controlling witch
-让你放弃所有你喜欢的东西 -不不
- that made you give up everything fun in your l-- - No. No.
你是那个拯救了我的女巫
You're the witch who saved me.
看 看这张照片
Look. Look at this picture.
现在看看这个人
Now look at this guy.
你不能告诉我说你的意见不重要
You can't tell me your opinion doesn't matter.
你用上百种方式使我变得更好
You changed me for the better in a hundred different ways.
是的 我或许错过了一本书或一份沙拉
Yeah, I-I might miss a book or a salad
七七八八的 但是
here and there, but...
但是我身上都是卡莱尔的印记
I've got Claire all over me.
等下我就会在你上面
You're about to.
这是世界上最难听的声音
That's the worst sound in the world.
是吗
Is it?
朋友们 亲人们 董事会的成员们
Friends, uh, family, uh, board members --
是很无聊啊
"Bored" is right.
我知道我们都很期待
I know we were all looking forward
欣赏一场美妙的竖琴演奏
to hearing the beautiful stylings of harp attack,
但是很不辛 有点小小的...
but there has, unfortunately, been a slight --
先别开始
Don't start yet!
推迟
delay,
节目会在几分钟后准时开始
and the program will start in a few minutes, on time.
请大家就坐吧
Uh, so, please, everyone take their seats.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 你做到了
Oh, my god, you did it!
算是吧
Sort of.
我知道这不是你盼望的那样
I know this isn't what you were hoping for,
但在聆听方面 我必须做的更好
but I need to do a better job of listening to you.
不不 你尽了全力
No, no, you did the best you could,
再说了 这可比去年安德鲁的"大提琴潜水艇"
and, plus, this is double what Andrew had last year
出席人数多了一倍
for "Cello submarine."
谢谢你
Thank you.
在如此叫好的时刻
Oh -- how are you sitting at a harp
坐在竖琴前的你们怎能不表示一下呢 女士们
and not scoring this moment? Ladies!
如果你不是一个好的聆听者
You can't have a successful marriage
那么你就不会有美满的婚姻
without being a good listener.
有时候得费点小功夫
Sometimes it takes a little work...
我只是想知道 他们会怎么
I just wonder what they're gonna do
对待他们的生命 你知道吗
with their lives, you know?
我只是想知道 他们是如何
I just wonder how they can actually, you know,
找到与竖琴之间的感应
ever find their true calling with a harp.
有时候得花点大功夫
...sometimes it takes a lot of work...
竖琴
Harps!
有时候它只是痛苦
...and sometimes it's just excruciating.
杰 过来 我又学会一首歌了
Jay, come. I work out another song.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
不
No!
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
我再也忍受不了了
I can't take it anymore!
好吗 这不是唱歌 这是鬼叫
Okay? It's not singing, it's screaming.
妈妈 我爱你 但是看在上帝的份上
Mom, I love you, but for the love of god,
在它毁了这个家之前把这个毁了
destroy that thing before it destroys this family!
胆小鬼
Coward!
我认为你唱的很不错
I think you sound great,
但是这吵到孩子的话
but if it bothers e kid...
胆小鬼
Coward!
丹尼 孩子
Oh Danny boy
那笛声在呼唤着你
The pipes, the pipes are calling
从一个峡谷到另一个峡谷 到了山的那头
From glen to glen, and down the mountain side
夏天已远去 所有的玫瑰...
The summer's gone, and all the roses...
你继续这样的话
You keep this up,
这就不会是我拔的最后一个插头
and this won't be the last plug I pull.